http://www.thepinksugarmouse.com/customer/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Customer Services - ThePinkSugarMouse.com
ThePinkSugarMouse.com
Close
Browse ThePinkSugarMouse.com
Freshly Made Fudge (Selection)
Our Sweets
Bonbons and Toffees
Chocolate (Coated and Centred)
Coconut Ice, Nuts and Ginger
Crystallised Fondants and Marzipan Fruits
Fudge (Selection Boxes)
Fudge (Individual Pieces)
Gluten Free Fudge
Gluten Free (Handmade)
Gluten Free Sweets
No Added Sugar
No Added Sugar (Chocolate Bars and Biscuits)
Search ThePinkSugarMouse.com
You are here:
Terms and Conditions
Security and Privacy PolicyYour privacy is of paramount importance to us, and we will never release your personal details to any outside company for mailing or marketing purposes. When you make a purchase from our website we will need to collect certain personal information from you to enable us to carry through the order quickly and effectively: We will ask, where applicable, for your full name, company name, phone number, e-mail address and payment method. We will need details of your billing address and, if different, the shipping address. This information will be stored and used by us as applicable.Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer&rsquos hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognise your browser and to provide you with some of our features. This cookie that is saved to your system, is only valid for a single visit and each new visit will result in a new cookie overwriting any previous that were generated on previous visits to our site.ThePinkSugarMouse.com complies fully with all applicable GDPR and consumer legislation, and will treat all your personal information as fully confidential. In order to serve you with the utmost efficiency, reputable third-party banking and distribution institutions handle our credit card transactions and order fulfilment. They receive the information needed to verify and authorise your payment card and to process your order. All such organisations are under strict obligation to keep your personal information private.
Customer Services
FAQs
Contact us
Terms and Conditions
Privacy policy
Browse ThePinkSugarMouse.com
Retro SweetsFree From RangeGluten Free FudgeGluten Free (Handmade)Gluten Free SweetsNo Added SugarNo Added Sugar (Chocolate Bars and Biscuits)Sugar Free SweetsSuitable for VegetariansSuitable for VeganChristmas Sweets
Our SweetsBonbons and ToffeesChocolate (Coated and Centred)Coconut Ice, Nuts and GingerCrystallised Fondants and Marzipan FruitsFudge (Selection Boxes)Fudge (Individual Pieces)Gums, Chews, Jellies and CandiesHard Boiled SweetsHumbugs, Rock and Flavoured SticksLiquoriceMints and AniseedNougatTurkish DelightSherbet and Sour SweetsAmerican SweetsOur ChocolatesOur Sweet HampersChristmas HampersAll Other HampersGift Ideas & BiscuitsChristmas IdeasWedding Favors - Sweet BuffetsBiscuits
Send us an Email
Like us on Facebook
Follow us on Twitter
Follow us on Instagram
© 2020 ThePinkSugarMouse.com
